ACTWU Publications 5619 PUBS
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Box: 1, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: The Inheritance, Publication (Box 1, Folder 36)
    By Millard Lampell; Robert Ryan; Harold Mayer. Adapted from the 50th Anniversary Film of the ACWA. Item is in English.
- Box: 1, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: In the matter of Arbitration Between ACTWU and ILGWU, Publication (Box 1, Folder 37)
    By Lane Kirkland. Concerning the Merger Agreement to be Effective July 1, 1995. Item is in English.
- Box: 1, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Introducing ACTOR-O: Optical Discount Program, Publication (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Box: 1, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Introducing ACTOR RxPlus: Your Complete Discount Mail-Order Pharmacy, Publication (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Item 2: Introducing ACTOR RxPlus: Your Complete Discount Mail-Order Pharmacy, Publication (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Box: 1, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Introductory Traning for Social Services Committees, Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Box: 1, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Iqbal Masih Had A Dream, Publication (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Box: 1, Folder: 42, Publication (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: It's Your Right To Organize a Union, Publication (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Box: 1, Folder: 43, Publication (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: Juntos en la Prevencion: Manual de Salud y Seguridad Para Sindicatos Locales, Publication (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Box: 1, Folder: 44, Publication (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: Lista Comprobatoria De Cuestiones De Salud y Seguridad, Publication (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Box: 1, Folder: 45, Publication (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 1, Folder 45)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.75:no.6 (1989:July/Aug.). Item is in English;Spanish.
- Box: 1, Folder: 46, Publication (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Item 1: LRA's 18th Annual Labor Awards Dinner, Honoring Jack Sheinkman, Publication (Box 1, Folder 46)
    By LRA (Labor Research Association). December 16, 1993. Item is in English.
- Box: 1, Folder: 47, Publication (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Item 1: Make a Smart Professional Move: Barneys Did!, Publication (Box 1, Folder 47)
    By Retail Clothing Salesmen's Union, Local 340. Reprinted from Labor Unity. Item is in English.
- Box: 1, Folder: 48, Publication (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Item 1: Making Leaflets, Publication (Box 1, Folder 48)
    By Paul Filson. Item is in English.
- Box: 1, Folder: 49, Publication (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Item 1: Meet the Amalgamated, Publication (Box 1, Folder 49)
    By ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America). Item is in English.
- Box: 1, Folder: 50, Publication (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Item 1: My Job Is a Pain In the... ! What Can I Do?, Publication (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Box: 1, Folder: 51, Publication (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Item 1: The Naked Truth About Unions, Publication (Box 1, Folder 51)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). Based on v.24:No.1 of the UAW AMMO. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Naked Truth About Unions, Publication (Box 1, Folder 51)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). Based on v.24:No.1 of the UAW AMMO. Copy 2. Item is in English.
- Box: 1, Folder: 52, Publication (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Item 1: New York ACTWU Worker Education Program, Publication (Box 1, Folder 52)
- Box: 1, Folder: 53, Publication (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Item 1: Our History / Nuestra Historia / Notre Histoire, Publication (Box 1, Folder 53)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). Photocopy. Item is in English;Spanish;French.
- Box: 1, Folder: 54, Publication (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Item 1: OSHA Law Reform, Publication (Box 1, Folder 54)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). Reprinted from Labor Unity, November - December, 1991. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: OSHA Law Reform, Publication (Box 1, Folder 54)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). Reprinted from Labor Unity, November - December, 1991. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: OSHA Law Reform, Publication (Box 1, Folder 54)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). Reprinted from Labor Unity, November - December, 1991. Copy 3. Item is in English.
- Box: 1, Folder: 55, Publication (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Item 1: Partners in Prevention: Health and Safety Action Manual for Local Unions., Publication (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Box: 1, Folder: 56, Publication (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Item 1: Peace on Earth, Publication (Box 1, Folder 56)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). Holiday card. Cover in many languages. Item is in English.
- Box: 1, Folder: 57, Publication (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Item 1: Program for Unemployed Members, Publication (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Box: 1, Folder: 58, Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Item 1: RxPlus, Publication (Box 1, Folder 58)
    By ACTOR (Amalgamated Clothing and Texitle Organization of Retirees). Important Information on Discount Pharmacy Service. Item is in English.
- Box: 1, Folder: 59, Publication (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Item 1: The Right-To-Know Guide: Our Legal Rights To Workplace Health and Safety Information, Publication (Box 1, Folder 59)
- Box: 1, Folder: 60, Publication (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Item 1: Safety and Health Checklist, Publication (Box 1, Folder 60)
- Box: 1, Folder: 61, Publication (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Item 1: Safety Committees: First Defense Against Job Hazards, Publication (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Item 2: ACTWU Safety and Health Department: How We Can Help You, Publication (Box 1, Folder 61)
- Box: 1, Folder: 62, Publication (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Item 1: Se Doa Ou Pou Ou Organize Yon Union, Publication (Box 1, Folder 62)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). Item is in Haitian Creole.
- Box: 1, Folder: 63, Publication (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Item 1: Sexual Harrassment: It's Against the Law., Publication (Box 1, Folder 63)
- Box: 1, Folder: 64, Publication (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Item 1: Shop Talk, Publication (Box 1, Folder 64)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). New York Joint Board Working Student Newsletter. no.4 (1990:Dec.). Item is in English.
- Box: 1, Folder: 65, Publication (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Item 1: Shop Talk, Publication (Box 1, Folder 65)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). New York Joint Board Working Student Newsletter. no.5 (1991:June). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Shop Talk, Publication (Box 1, Folder 65)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). New York Joint Board Working Student Newsletter. Special Holiday Edition (1991:Dec.). Item is in English.
- Box: 1, Folder: 66, Publication (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Item 1: Shop Talk, Publication (Box 1, Folder 66)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). New York Joint Board Working Student Newsletter. New Year's Resolutions Isue (1992:Jan.). Item is in English.
- Box: 1, Folder: 67, Publication (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Item 1: Shop Talk, Publication (Box 1, Folder 67)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). New York Joint Board Working Student Newsletter. December, 1993. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Shop Talk, Publication (Box 1, Folder 67)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). New York Joint Board Working Student Newsletter. December, 1993. Copy 2. Item is in English.
- Box: 1, Folder: 68, Publication (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Item 1: Shop Talk, Publication (Box 1, Folder 68)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). New York Joint Board Working Student Newsletter. January, 1994. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Shop Talk, Publication (Box 1, Folder 68)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). New York Joint Board Working Student Newsletter. January, 1994. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Shop Talk, Publication (Box 1, Folder 68)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). New York Joint Board Working Student Newsletter. February, 1994. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Shop Talk, Publication (Box 1, Folder 68)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). New York Joint Board Working Student Newsletter. February, 1994. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Shop Talk, Publication (Box 1, Folder 68)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). New York Joint Board Working Student Newsletter. March, 1994. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Shop Talk, Publication (Box 1, Folder 68)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). New York Joint Board Working Student Newsletter. March, 1994. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Shop Talk, Publication (Box 1, Folder 68)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). New York Joint Board Working Student Newsletter. April, 1994. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Shop Talk, Publication (Box 1, Folder 68)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). New York Joint Board Working Student Newsletter. May, 1994. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Shop Talk, Publication (Box 1, Folder 68)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). New York Joint Board Working Student Newsletter. May, 1994. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Shop Talk, Publication (Box 1, Folder 68)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). New York Joint Board Working Student Newsletter. June, 1994. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Shop Talk, Publication (Box 1, Folder 68)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). New York Joint Board Working Student Newsletter. November, 1994. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Shop Talk, Publication (Box 1, Folder 68)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). New York Joint Board Working Student Newsletter. November, 1994. Copy 2. Item is in English.
- Box: 1, Folder: 69, Publication (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Item 1: Shop Talk, Publication (Box 1, Folder 69)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). New York Joint Board Working Student Newsletter. January, 1995. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Shop Talk, Publication (Box 1, Folder 69)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). New York Joint Board Working Student Newsletter. January, 1995. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Shop Talk, Publication (Box 1, Folder 69)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). New York Joint Board Working Student Newsletter. April, 1995. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Shop Talk, Publication (Box 1, Folder 69)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). New York Joint Board Working Student Newsletter. May, 1995. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Shop Talk, Publication (Box 1, Folder 69)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). New York Joint Board Working Student Newsletter. May, 1995. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Shop Talk, Publication (Box 1, Folder 69)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). New York Joint Board Working Student Newsletter. May, 1995. Copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Shop Talk, Publication (Box 1, Folder 69)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). New York Joint Board Working Student Newsletter. June, 1995. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Shop Talk, Publication (Box 1, Folder 69)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). New York Joint Board Working Student Newsletter. June, 1995. Copy 2. Item is in English.
- Box: 1, Folder: 70, Publication (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Item 1: ACTWU Social Services: At Work and In The Community, Publication (Box 1, Folder 70)
- Box: 1, Folder: 71, Publication (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Item 1: Information and Referral Skills for ACTWU Social Services Committee Members, Publication (Box 1, Folder 71)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). Guidelines. Item is in English.
- Box: 1, Folder: 72, Publication (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Item 1: ACTWU Stewards' Handbook, Publication (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Item 2: ACTWU Stewards' Handbook, Publication (Box 1, Folder 72)
- Box: 1, Folder: 73, Publication (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Item 1: Stopping Sexual Harrassment at Work, Publication (Box 1, Folder 73)
- Box: 1, Folder: 74, Publication (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Item 1: Stop the Pain! A Workers' Guide To Job Design, Publication (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Item 2: Stop the Pain! A Workers' Guide To Job Design, Publication (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Item 3: Stop the Pain! A Workers' Guide To Job Design, Publication (Box 1, Folder 74)
- Box: 1, Folder: 75, Publication (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Item 1: Guia Al Diseno Del Trabajo: Para El Trabajador, Publication (Box 1, Folder 75)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). Short version. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 2: Stop the Pain! A Workers' Guide To Job Design, Publication (Box 1, Folder 75)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). Short version. Item is in English.
- Box: 1, Folder: 76, Publication (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Item 1: A Strategy for Innovation, Publication (Box 1, Folder 76)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). September, 1991. Report of the ACTWU/CMA National Clothing Industry Labor-Management Committee. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: A Strategy for Innovation, Publication (Box 1, Folder 76)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). September, 1991. Report of the ACTWU/CMA National Clothing Industry Labor-Management Committee. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: A Strategy for Innovation, Publication (Box 1, Folder 76)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). September, 1991. Report of the ACTWU/CMA National Clothing Industry Labor-Management Committee. Copy 3. Item is in English.
- Box: 1, Folder: 77, Publication (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Item 1: Strike Assistance For Local Unions: How To Set Up A Strike Assistance Program, Publication (Box 1, Folder 77)
- Box: 1, Folder: 78, Publication (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Item 1: Syracuse, Utica, Batavia, Rochester, Geneva, Publication (Box 1, Folder 78)
    By Rochester Joint Board. Item is in English.
- Box: 1, Folder: 79, Publication (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Item 1: Testimony: Justice vs. J. P. Stevens, Publication (Box 1, Folder 79)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). From the Film. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Testimony: Justice vs. J. P. Stevens, Publication (Box 1, Folder 79)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). Boycott J. P. Stevens Products. Item is in English.
- Box: 1, Folder: 80, Publication (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Item 1: This Is Your ACTWU Member's Kit, Publication (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Item 2: This Is Your ACTWU Member's Kit, Publication (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Item 3: This Is Your ACTWU Member's Kit, Publication (Box 1, Folder 80)
- Box: 1, Folder: 81, Publication (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Item 1: This Is Your Union, Esta Es Su Union: ACTWU, Publication (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Item 2: This Is Your Union, Esta Es Su Union: ACTWU, Publication (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Item 3: This Is Your Union, Esta Es Su Union: ACTWU, Publication (Box 1, Folder 81)
- Box: 1, Folder: 82, Publication (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Item 1: Trick or Treat?, Publication (Box 1, Folder 82)
- Box: 1, Folder: 83, Publication (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Item 1: Unemployed? ACTWU Members Are Doing Something About It, Publication (Box 1, Folder 83)
- Box: 1, Folder: 84, Publication (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Item 1: A Union Handbook for Getting Our Stories in the Media, Publication (Box 1, Folder 84)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). How Come That Lady's Kid Is On the News, When My Kid Is Cuter?. Item is in English.
- Box: 1, Folder: 85, Publication (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Item 1: Union Predicts Company Tricks: Will They Be Right or Wrong? You Keep Score, Publication (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Item 2: Union Predicts Company Tricks: Will They Be Right or Wrong? You Keep Score, Publication (Box 1, Folder 85)
- Box: 1, Folder: 86, Publication (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Item 1: United In Purpose, United In Action, A Strong Voice for Working People: ACTWU AMO, Publication (Box 1, Folder 86)
    By AMO (Associated Membership Organization). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: United In Purpose, United In Action, A Strong Voice for Working People: ACTWU AMO, Publication (Box 1, Folder 86)
    By AMO (Associated Membership Organization). Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: United In Purpose, United In Action, A Strong Voice for Working People: ACTWU AMO, Publication (Box 1, Folder 86)
    By AMO (Associated Membership Organization). Copy 3. Item is in English.
- Box: 1, Folder: 87, Publication (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Item 1: Victory Celebration, Publication (Box 1, Folder 87)
    By Washable Clothing, Sportswear and Novelty Workers Local 169. January 31, 1942. Item is in English.
- Box: 1, Folder: 88, Publication (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Item 1: We Are Workers and Students: ACTWU Local 292, Publication (Box 1, Folder 88)
- Box: 1, Folder: 89, Publication (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Item 1: Welcome Delegates, Alternates, Guests, Publication (Box 1, Folder 89)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). Fifth Constitutional Convention, Miami Beach, FL, June 4-8, 1990. Item is in English.
- Box: 1, Folder: 90, Publication (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Item 1: Welcome To ACTWU: Fighting For Our Future, Publication (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Item 2: Welcome To ACTWU: Fighting For Our Future, Publication (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Item 3: Welcome To ACTWU: Fighting For Our Future, Publication (Box 1, Folder 90)
- Box: 1, Folder: 91, Publication (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Item 1: Bienvenidos a ACTWU: Luchando Por Nuestro Futuro, Publication (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Item 2: Bienvenidos a ACTWU: Luchando Por Nuestro Futuro, Publication (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Item 3: Bienvenidos a ACTWU: Luchando Por Nuestro Futuro, Publication (Box 1, Folder 91)
- Box: 1, Folder: 92, Publication (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Item 1: Welcome To The ACTWU First Constitutional Convention, Publication (Box 1, Folder 92)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). Los Angeles, CA, September 25-29, 1978. Item is in English.
- Box: 1, Folder: 93, Publication (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - Item 1: Welcome To Your Union: ACTWU, Publication (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - Item 2: Welcome To Your Union: ACTWU, Publication (Box 1, Folder 93)
- Box: 1, Folder: 94, Publication (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - Item 1: What To Do If You Lose Your Job, Publication (Box 1, Folder 94)
    By Grace W. Weinstein. Public Affairs Pamphlet no.617. Item is in English.
- Box: 1, Folder: 95, Publication (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - Item 1: Workers' Compensation: A Union Responsibility, Publication (Box 1, Folder 95)
- Box: 1, Folder: 96, Publication (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - Item 1: Ya Es Usted El Delegado, Publication (Box 1, Folder 96)
    By Mary Elkuss. Item is in Spanish.
- Box: 1, Folder: 97, Publication (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - Item 1: You May Be Retiring From Your Job, But You Don't Have to Retire From Your Union: Join ACTOR, Publication (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - Item 2: You May Be Retiring From Your Job, But You Don't Have to Retire From Your Union: Join ACTOR, Publication (Box 1, Folder 97)
- Box: 1, Folder: 98, Publication (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - Item 1: Your Union at Work: Its Structure and Collective Bargaining Role, Publication (Box 1, Folder 98)
    By ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America). Reprinted from Profile of a Union. Item is in English.
- Box: 1, Folder: 99, Publication (Box 1, Folder 99)
  - Item 1: Index to Advance, 1928-1929, Publication (Box 1, Folder 99)
- Box: 1, Folder: 100, Publication (Box 1, Folder 100)
  - Item 1: Annual Awards Banquet, Publication (Box 1, Folder 100)
    By Eugene V. Debs Foundation. November 12, 1988. Honoring Joyce Miller. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Annual Awards Banquet, Publication (Box 1, Folder 100)
    By Eugene V. Debs Foundation. November 12, 1988. Honoring Joyce Miller. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Annual Awards Banquet, Publication (Box 1, Folder 100)
    By Eugene V. Debs Foundation. November 12, 1988. Honoring Joyce Miller. Copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Debs Foundation Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 100)
    By Eugene V. Debs Foundation. Fall 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Debs Foundation Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 100)
    By Eugene V. Debs Foundation. Fall 1988. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Debs Foundation Newsletter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 100)
    By Eugene V. Debs Foundation. Fall 1988. Copy 3. Item is in English.
- Box: 2, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.73:no.5 (1987:May). Item is in English;Spanish;French.
  - Item 2: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.73:no.6 (1987:June). Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.73:no.7 (1987:July/Aug.). Item is in English;Spanish.
  - Item 4: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.73:no.8 (1987:Sept.). Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.73:no.9 (1987:Oct.). Item is in English;French.
  - Item 6: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.73:no.9 (1987:Oct.). Copy 2. Item is in English;French.
  - Item 7: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.73:no.10 (1987:Nov.). Item is in English;Spanish;French.
  - Item 8: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.73:no.11 (1987:Dec.). Item is in English;Spanish;French.
- Box: 2, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.74:no.3 (1988:Mar.). Item is in English;French.
  - Item 2: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.74:no.4 (1988:Apr.). Item is in English;Spanish;French.
  - Item 3: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.74:no.5 (1988:May). Item is in English;Spanish;French.
  - Item 4: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.74:no.6 (1988:June). Item is in English;Spanish;French.
  - Item 6: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.74:no.7 (1988:July/Aug.). Item is in English;Spanish;French.
  - Item 7: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.74:no.8 (1988:Sept.). Item is in English;Spanish;French.
  - Item 8: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.74:no.9 (1988:Oct.). Item is in English;Spanish;French.
  - Item 9: Labor Unity, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    By ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union). v.74:no.10 (1988:Nov.). Item is in English;Spanish;French.